Good morning. It's Saturday, February
28th, 2026. I'm Ted Rall. That's John
Kiriakou. You're watching a special
extra unscheduled edition of the program
with Ted Rall and John Kiriakou.
As you probably already know this
morning, the United States and Israel
have launched a war against Iran. The
president
is calling for the overthrow of the
Iranian government, and the casualty
figures are already quite high. Bomb
blasts have been felt throughout Tehran.
John,
I'm sorry to see you on Saturday morning
under such circumstances, but it's good
to see you.
Ted, my friend Genie just texted me from
Florida to say that the Dish Network
has blocked Al Jazeera from broadcasting
here in the United States.
They don't want us to see what's
happening in the Middle East. We know
from CNN
and from other sources, the New York
Times is reporting that
that an Israeli missile hit a girl's
school in southern Iran this morning
killing 57 children. So, get used to
that. That's going to be what this war
looks like. The Israelis don't give a
[__] about human life, about civilians,
and we're going to see a lot of civilian
casualties. On the flip side,
the Iranians said days ago, even as long
as a week ago, that if there were going
to be attack an attack, they would
strike US assets around the Persian
Gulf. They have done exactly that. They
have hit the US military base in Kuwait.
They've hit the center of Manama,
Bahrain, the capital of Bahrain. They've
hit Abu Dhabi. There was an a missile
intercepted over Dubai.
This is a real war. This isn't going to
be just, you know, a back and forth
tete-a-tete over the next 24 hours. This
is a conflagration.
Yeah, that's how I see it, too. I mean,
I don't see it any other way, but the
president is is predicting or the
administration, I should say, is
predicting just a few days of of
conflict. I don't see how that's
possible. I mean, with the Iranians
peace in Ukraine by now, so
24 hours for that.
Right. Well, the Iranians are engaged in
existential battle for their for their
government and for their country and for
they don't want to go the way of
Venezuela and become a vassal state.
They're going to fight back hard with
everything they've got and that's
inevitably going to cause the United
States and Israel to play the victim,
even though they started all this. And
and they're going to say, you know,
well, you know, look at what the
dastardly Iranians did. We have to
retaliate, even though, you know,
they're the ones that should be
retaliated against.
You know, I'm seeing I'm seeing from
Joseph Roy 7021 that Comcast Xfinity is
also blocking Al Jazeera. That's up in
the Boston area. So,
that's they don't do that just on a whim
or by accident. They're doing it because
the administration asked them to. And
Cena, this is going to be an ongoing
theme.
We should probably talk about this for a
minute. This is going to be a theme
about about only allowing the American
people to get the information that the
government wants them to get.
I watch Al Jazeera every day. Yeah,
it's the only game in town when it comes
to you know, video from Gaza. There's no
one else. That's it. That's it. So, I
mean, already Al Jazeera America was
shut down by the Bush administration
effectively.
You know, not officially, but they
leaned on the cable
companies so that they couldn't
effectively have an outlet.
You know, we've seen that over and over
here in the US. I mean, you know, we're
the land of the free my ass. And you
know,
if truth is the first casualty of war,
the first thing you want to do is is
kill the truth or kill any other
narrative. Um,
John, there's going to be so much to get
into and and as usual, even though this
is a special edition, please go ahead
and post your questions.
If you're watching live right now in the
9:00 hour on Saturday morning
into the live feed and into the rumble
room and we will get to all of those if
we can, but we're going to try. Um, Ted,
I want to ask you a question. Yeah.
Yeah,
Donald Trump said
last night that this was going to be a
massive, his words, a massive and
ongoing
military [snorts] campaign.
And he also called it major combat
operations. Now, those those words have
very specific meanings
in in war.
That means troops on the ground. That is
what it means.
>> mean that or or is he just
talking?
>> know. I don't know how much he's been
briefed on, you know, what the
appropriate
vocabulary is here. You know, he's not a
a man of careful language and parsing
language. So, you know, with him, you
have to kind of read less into it than
you would with a normal president, I
think is is fair to say, right? When
but it's hard to imagine US troops on
the ground in Iran.
Like, how do what does that look like? I
mean, it's you and I have talked about
this many times, John. It is a massive
country.
It is
It's
you know, the Iranian people might may
or may not like their government. It's
not the most popular government, but
what's a lot less popular is the idea of
a US occupation or invasion. They don't
want that, for sure. No one wants that.
Um, and so I can't even imagine. I mean,
uh,
and also, I got to say, this is the part
that chilled me to the bones.
It's the fact that Israel the United
States are now so intertwined in this
massive, um, endeavor for lack of a
better word. I mean, we're really joined
at the hip now. I mean, this is
basically telling the entire Muslim
world, um, we are one in the same. And
what Israel does is what the US does and
vice versa. Um, you know, Israel is
wildly unpopular even here in the United
States, but it's certainly around the
world. Um, you know, for the first time
yesterday there was a poll that showed
that most Americans sympathize with the
Palestinian cause more than Israelis.
First time in since 1948. Um, this is,
you know, we just crawled climbed into
bed with, you know, with Bibi Netanyahu
who's a [__] monster and everybody
thinks is a monster.
I don't even know where to begin. I I'm
looking at reactions from around the
world right now and
every one of our of our
NATO allies has either expressed
condemnation
or regret.
Uh, the only countries that are
condemning Iran's retaliation are the
countries that are being hit by Iranian
missiles, but
Ted, looking at the map that you just
put up,
these these attacks are literally all
over Iran. At least all over the
populated part of Iran. Right.
>> this this really is massive. This isn't
just Tehran and maybe some military
bases. It is all over the country.
Yeah, it is. And look, for people who
haven't been to Tehran, I have. Um, it
is a big country. It's bigger than New
York, I mean, it's a big city. It's
bigger than New York City. Um, it has a
population of 9.7 million people in the
city proper plus significant, you know,
huge sprawling suburbs. Um, it is, you
know, this is a densely populated city.
Um, the all all major Iranian cities
are. They're very modern. Um, you know,
it's this is going to be a war against
the civilian population as much as it is
a war against quote and quote military
targets. Look, that's a very important
point. Yes. This this really is this
this is going to be a war against
civilians. And we saw that right off the
bat. We know we know how little the
Israelis care about civilians because
none of us have been blind as we watched
the the the genocide in Gaza. But they
are perfectly happy to kill as many
Iranian civilians as they possibly can.
No, that's that's true. You know, look,
they've been chomping at the bit. Um,
you know, as an American I also second
look, my first my first thought is with
the people of Iran who do not deserve
this, did not and did not provoke this,
did not ask for this. And even their
government was conned and fooled by a
President Trump who you know, engaged
the Omanis to you know, to conduct
diplomacy to try to bring this in for a
soft landing. Um, basically lied and
said that the there were several weeks
to resolve this
and then basically launched a sneaky a
dastardly sneak attack. It's kind of
similar to what the US accused Japan of
when right before Pearl Harbor. It's
like, guys, why did you attack? We were
negotiating.
>> That's right. And you know, and look at
the reporting. It's only early now, but
reporting on you know, this was supposed
to be apparently a decapitation strike
where we take out Ayatollah Khamenei
with the administration not
understanding
that taking out Ayatollah Khamenei
>> does nothing. isn't going to do
anything. No. Nothing, literally
nothing.
I mean, no, it really it really won't. I
mean, it's it's not Iran is not a
dictatorship. And you know, it's like
over
you they and also trying to kill him.
It's like, well, there's no coming back
from that. You bombed the guy's
compound. You tried to kill him.
Um you know, I mean, you guys already,
you know, did that to Soleimani. I mean,
you know, the Iranians know exactly
where they stand. And Trump also brought
up Soleimani
uh last night
uh reiterating how good it was that he
had killed him, how important it was
that he killed him, and and that we were
going to we were going to cut the head
off the uh the Iranian leadership.
That's just not the case. The Iranians
are incredibly resilient. Yeah, they
are. And not to mention, they have this
unique series of overlapping
governmental structures, right? That is
uniquely Persian/Iranian, right? Where
they have um a lot of redundancy built
into the system, which can cause like,
you know, bureaucratic inefficiency, and
it's hard to make decisions. But, in a
situation like this, when you're being
attacked by um a foreign adversary, it's
incredibly useful. They have redundant
governmental structures throughout the
system. I mean, you know, they can they
you can take out big swaths of the
Iranian government. It's not going to
make any difference. No, it's not. DH
Frank has a great question. Wartime
presidents typically get major bumps in
approval. I think this war will do the
opposite. Agreed. What do you What do
you say? I totally agree. We talked
yesterday or day before yesterday, we
talked about a split within the
Republican Party between the America
First Anti-War MAGA right, and you know,
the John McCain wing of the party, which
is rearing its ugly head again. And um I
think this is going to be different. I
think this is going to seriously hurt
Donald Trump. I'm going to I would bet
money that that officials inside the
White House, inside the Executive Office
of the President, are wringing their
hands today saying that Donald Trump
just threw away any last hope of uh
of stemming Republican losses in the
midterm elections.
John, I'm 100% sure you're right about
that. And and and mainly for two main
reasons that come to mind while my
coffee, uh you know, sets in. Number
one,
uh we have um
the the the the MAGA wing of the GOP is
very clear in the polls that they feel
that the president has taken his eye off
the ball on immigration and on the
economy. Um this is only going to
confirm that, right? Um and also,
they're not pro-Israel. Then there's the
um and then there's the uh the domestic
side of this, which is the United States
is um
you know, just hold on. Let me Let me
I'm I need to like get into some of
these questions here. Um
Uh
How
Trump, the master of distraction and the
most fickle leader in history, I'm truly
worried. How long will this go on? Do
you think Iran will need to bow down for
it to end?
I think they're in it for to the death.
That's what I think, too. I think this
is like Iraq. It's uh Yeah. Yeah, it it
it it's really bad. Um look, in terms of
Trump's popularity, John, um this is
only going to hurt for one big reason.
There's been no run-up to this war,
right? There's been no lube before he
stuck it in. That which is part of the
reason that he snuck it in on a on a
Friday night news dump. I mean, the
American people have not been told that
Iran threatens them, has WMDs, is going
to kill them or their friends or
anything like that. I mean, there's been
no prep at all. Yeah.
>> So, this isn't at all like the the Bush
administration started scheming on 9/12
for an invasion that came a year and a
half later against Iraq. That And you
know, Afghanistan was easier because
again, the people forget that the
groundwork for invading Afghanistan had
already been laid from propaganda point
of view a year or two earlier because of
all the reports of the Taliban blowing
up the Bamiyan statues and all that and
like the the treatment of women. Um they
were all There was already the bombing
of the USS Cole in 2000, the embassy
bombings in in uh in in Kenya and
Tanzania in 1998. So, the American
people already thought of Afghanistan as
a bet noir.
They don't think of Iran as a bet noir.
They used to after the hostage crisis,
Sure. but that was half a century ago.
>> Generations ago. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Yeah, it's just not true anymore.
No, it's not not true anymore. Uh, let's
let's do some more questions. Pipsqueak
is asking, do we think any NATO country
will back this?
Mhm. You know what? I think I'm I'm
ashamed I'm ashamed to even say these
words.
Greece is going to back
Really?
>> Israel and the US. Yeah, because the
Greeks are broke. The Greeks are weak.
Cyprus is sitting on an ocean of natural
gas of which the Greeks have a portion.
They're lifting that gas with the
Israelis.
And I think the Greeks will do anything
the Israelis tell them to do. Now, that
is exactly the opposite of Greek public
opinion, which is solidly strongly with
the Palestinians on the Gaza issue, and
will likely be with the Iranians on on
this issue because of the Greek people's
opposition to to war in general.
That is insane. Um,
well, I mean, that's yeah. Well, that
that's a we'll have repercussions uh,
throughout the world, right? With US
allies and Gulf states and all that. Um,
talk about unpopular governments, how
about Trump's popularity, right? Which
is currently, depending on how you look
at it, between 36 and 38% the lowest of
his entire including his first term in
office, right? So, um, look, this is
going to look for MAGA world Oh, yeah, I
wanted to say this too, John. This is
going to look for some people in MAGA
world as a huge distract Epstein
distraction machine.
You bet it will.
You bet it will. It's funny, you look at
the Washington Post today, and of course
the banner is US and Israel attack Iran
as Trump calls for regime change, and
just underneath it's Musk asked Epstein
for quote the wildest party, now he says
he stands up for victims. So without
this this war this this
attack, you know what the headline was
going to be.
Yes, that's true.
Yeah.
It was Yeah. No, I mean yeah.
And you know, I mean look, obviously
this was planned. John, you called it
weeks ago. You said, you know, you you
quoted the guy who um you know, who who
trained you originally at this at the
agency and said, you know, you don't
send carrier battle groups in if you
don't plan to use them, right? Am I
paraphrasing correctly?
There's
one of our viewers very generously um
uh emailed me last week to say that
there was a there was a podcaster
talking [__] about me.
And maybe I should uh respond. So I
looked at it and he was really talking a
lot of [__] about me.
Um but it was about
what I said a week ago
a week and a half ago that
a friend of mine at the White House said
that a decision had been made to attack
Iran, that it would come this past
Monday or Tuesday. Obviously it was
delayed a few days, but that the
decision had been made. And then he was
like, how the [__] does this guy know?
He's been out of the CIA for 20 years.
What are we supposed to believe that
people who have access to the
information just call him and offer it
up?
Yeah.
They do.
Because they're opposed to war.
So yeah.
There's a major serious split in the
American government over this. One of
the things that surprised me when I woke
up this morning, Ted, was to see how
many US senators of both parties
are condemning this action. Donald Trump
didn't go to Congress and asked and
asked to invoke the uh
the uh what do you call it act the uh Oh
my god, I'm blanking. I'm so mad right
now.
The to send forces to the Middle East.
Oh, the War Powers Act.
>> War Powers Act, thank you. Just had
force in the Middle East and there
certainly has been no congressional
declaration of war.
So, this is a war crime. It's illegal.
It's an illegal attack. And it's
completely unprovoked. I mean, there's
no approach. There's no attack by the
Iranians. There was no threat of of
imminent attack. There's no threat of
not imminent attack. The Iranians
already, you know, the main demand of
the United States was don't don't
develop nuclear weapons. The um the
Iranians said, "No worries. We don't
want to develop nuclear weapons."
They've been consistent about this since
the Islamic Revolution. They voluntarily
kept the um
their membership in the nuclear
non-proliferation pact that the Shah had
signed. They didn't have to. They could
have said, "We just had a revolution. We
don't have to keep this old treaty
obligation." But, they did. It Day
before yesterday, I was on a
Lebanese network called Al Mayadeen. I
love this station. It is such an
in-depth
I mean, it's in Arabic, of course, but
it's such an in-depth
news analysis station. I always say yes
when they ask me to go on. So,
uh usually they have me sort of uh
you know, as a point-counterpoint with a
professor. And they have fantastic uh
professors, especially on American
politics.
And um
and uh day before yesterday, they had me
debating the lead nego- the lead nuclear
negotiator from Iran. I was shocked when
he came on the screen and that's who I
was supposed to debate. But, he said the
same things that you just said. That the
Iranians are signatories to the nuclear
non-proliferation treaty. They allow
nuclear um
inspections.
It's the Israelis who have nukes, who
won't sign the NPT, and who have
forbidden any and all inspections. The
Iranians have always been willing to
play along with international law on
these issues and I made a I made a point
that at first he he rejected outright
and then finally came around and was
like, well, okay. I said, look, what
what the two sides are negotiating right
now
is the JCPOA.
True.
>> That's what it is.
It's all the same tenets that were in
the JCPOA.
>> That Trump scrapped. That Trump scrapped
unilaterally. Those points being that
Iran couldn't um
couldn't uh enrich uranium to weapons
grade.
That the uranium that they were
enriching as well as Iranian nuclear
sites had to be open to inspection by
the IAEA, which is the United Nations
body.
And that uh if they were going to enrich
uranium, they had to store the uranium
in a third country with the three
countries being considered being Saudi
Arabia, the United Arab Emirates and
Turkey.
And the Iranians were agreeing to all
that. Because they had agreed to it 15
years ago with Barack Obama. Yeah, the
only thing the Iranians did not agree to
was scrapping their uh medium-range
standard conventional missiles. And no
country in its right mind would ever
agree to something
>> No, they wouldn't. And the United
States, all that would be doing is
putting what happened uh last night and
this morning uh off uh uh for another
couple of years. That's all it would do,
maybe. Um so
>> Tariq, I'm sorry to interrupt you. Tariq
says Tariq, thanks for the buck. You say
something that that I say all the time.
It Is the US just a war economy?
Yes.
If if we were not at war somewhere in
the world, our economy would slip into
recession. And this has been the case
since the 9/11 attacks. That's how
everybody in Washington got rich.
It's been off of our constant full-time
war economy. Um Robbie, our producer,
has a question. I'm putting him on. Hi,
Robbie. Hey, no, I just have a quick
question and I've been wrestling with
this for a couple of days and I'm really
hoping that the two of you can can
answer it.
Mark Levin
keeps going out calling Tucker Carlson a
traitor Yeah. for opposing the strike on
Iran.
My question is is how can you be a
traitor if you oppose an action
perpetrated by another country? To be a
traitor means I'd be I would be actively
working against my country, not opposing
the geopolitics of another one. So then
by
then by that nature by that by that
logic, am I a traitor?
Right. And someone can someone explain
to me
>> It's like when they called Julian
Assange a traitor. Like a traitor, he's
Australian. What are you talking about?
Yeah, it's it's insane. I I don't get
it.
I I despise Trump. I I hate the man with
a burning I hate him.
When you've lost Robbie West, you're
done.
Seriously.
Um okay. Well, thanks Robbie for that.
Um let's do um let's do some more
questions here. You Yanks are in a civil
another civil war and the fascists are
winning. Better get your [__] together
or your democracy is dead. I'm sorry, I
think our democracy is on the way out
and I don't think there's any way to
save it. I agree.
Uh could this war expose US and Israeli
military weaknesses while driving
America's main rivals, Russia and China,
closer?
Those are Absolutely yes. And may I add
something about that? Please.
>> Um
when Iran sent the 600 drones
last October Mhm.
and the the vaunted Iron Dome shot all
of them out of the sky except for seven.
The fact that seven slow-motion drones
got through the Iron Dome was very
valuable military intelligence. It was a
probing attack basically.
>> attack and so the Iranians
>> was they gave and then the Israelis knew
it was coming, too. That's right. What
so what what do the Israelis do if the
Iranians launch a hypersonic against
them? Which they probably will. I would
if I were Iran. I would. Why not?
>> [snorts]
>> There's no reason. I mean, not to
mention I wouldn't feel terribly guilty.
The Israeli people
are behind Netanyahu. Yeah. I mean, the
stat- the statistics are are, you know,
the polling is very clear on that point.
I'm really sorry about to hear that. Um
will Russia and China be closer? Look,
Russia and China were getting closer
anyway. This is I I think this is part
of a This is on a continuum, right, of
US behavior that is forcing other
countries
Um right now, if I'm uh if I'm Modi in
India,
I'm kind of like holding my dick out in
the wind. Like I just I just came back
from, you know, hanging out with Bibi,
and it's like I'm not feeling too good
this morning.
No.
I agree. And, you know, this this
Russia-China
>> million Muslims in his country. Exactly
right.
Yeah, it's That's exactly right. Uh we
should uh we should keep a close eye on
the on the Chinese-Russian relationship,
too.
It
Iran is a BRICS country, as are China
and Russia. As that organization becomes
stronger, more fulsome, more inclusive,
um
we should expect to see a formal
alliance between the Russians, the
Chinese, and the um
and the uh uh Iranians. And then what do
we do? We're going to fight the Russians
and Chinese for Israel?
That. And John, I have a question for
you. Do you think um
what's the calculus here for Donald
Trump and the US government and his
administration? I mean, why is he doing
Netanyahu's bidding so slavishly?
You know, I I'm
I think that deep down Donald Trump is
an authoritarian.
I think that I think that he enjoys the
he enjoys looking like a military
strongman.
And I think that he doesn't actually
believe in anything. I don't think he
believes in
MAGA, you know, no war. I don't think he
has any core beliefs. And I think that
he thought that a quick decapitation
strike the Iranians would be dancing in
the streets thanking him and thanking
God, and he would go down in history as,
you know, as as Teddy Roosevelt. And
that's just simply not going to happen.
It was never going to happen. No. But he
was the only one that thought that it
would.
Scott Ritter said this morning, Stephen
says uh that we failed to kill the
Ayatollah in the strike. What
information do we have on this? Um
the Israelis are claiming that they
think that the Ayatollah Ali Khamenei
Khamenei was uh
injured. I think they're just talking
[__] and they don't have any idea. Um if
you're the I mean if you're the
Iranians, obviously they have they knew
that this was coming. They knew there
was a strong possibility this was
coming. I mean, they're not stupid. I
would have thought that he would be in a
in another location, no?
Yeah.
I and I'm sure that he was.
They're not stupid.
No. Uh I
So, I guess Donald does not does not
want the video of him [__] a child
released, so he'll continue to obey the
orders of his Zionist masters.
Netanyahu released a statement saying
he's backing the Iranian people to
overthrow the regime. Oh, I'm sure
they're taking lots of cues from him. At
the same time, he's sending cruise
missiles into schools, apartment
buildings, and hospitals. Yeah, they
love him.
Um what would the purpose of extended
boots on the ground campaign be to uh
for extending war powers for the
president?
Well, he would have to go to Congress. I
mean, he has to go to Congress.
>> He has to go to Congress. If he if
there's any respect left whatsoever for
the Constitution.
Yeah. Which there may not be.
>> And and Congress isn't going to give him
authorization to put boots on the
ground.
Um
>> No way. And remember what we said last
week, George W. Bush in the in the weeks
and months before the attack on Iraq, he
crisscrossed the country to swing public
opinion. Donald Trump has done literally
nothing to swing public opinion.
Nothing.
>> Yeah. That's why That's why this will
not work. You can't fight a war that
causes Americans to come home in body
bags and and cost the taxpayer billions
of dollars and provokes future terrorist
attacks without getting the American
people behind you. Um even if you do,
that support may not last as people like
uh you know, LBJ and Richard Nixon and
and George W. Bush are well aware. But
at least you have to start with it and
you know you're going to like that
support's going to blow out like a like
a like a like a tide ebbing, right? But
that's not He's not starting with that.
Nobody wants this war. There's literally
no contin- There's no constituency for
it. No, there's no constituency for it.
Thank you very much for the uh 200 uh
I guess those are um Emirati uh
uh Dirhams. Dirhams, yeah. I always want
to say dinars. Um thank you very much
for that. Um thanks for the fiver. I
thought I sent him, I guess Trump,
campaign money because I thought he was
scummy enough to double-cross Israel.
Boy, was I wrong.
Um We've had that conversation with
Robbie. We did. To what extent George
Tenet 421 wants to know, uh does it seem
that Israeli special ops and assets have
been expended in a 12-day war and
protests already? And by the way, John,
that's a good question, right? I mean,
the United States um is running low on
materiel because it gave to so many
bombs, especially dumb bombs, but also
big bunker busters to Israel to destroy
Gaza with. That's right.
So, that indicates to me that they have
other weapons in mind.
Yeah, I have to agree. It's It's been no
secret that we're short of munitions.
And the Israelis were short of
munitions. That's why there was no
attack on Iran a month ago or 2 months
ago. They were short of munitions.
>> Iran's going to obviously be subject to
They're going to go after their
infrastructure. They're going to It's
like massive cyber attacks already
underway, an Israeli specialty.
Um
That's They're going to They're They're
going to try to bring them to their
knees that way.
I don't think it's going to work, but I
I agree with you. We'll see.
>> I I don't think it is going to work. Uh
Cutter airspace is closed. I was about
to fly to Europe tomorrow with a
stopover in Cutter. Yeah, the airports
in um
in Kuwait, Dhahran, Bahrain, Cutter, Abu
Dhabi, and Dubai are all closed.
No flights in or out. I was just there a
week ago. I just can't
can't believe it. Robbie's asking do we
think Russia and China will assist Iran
militarily or are they on their own?
They're on their own. Yeah.
Unfortunately.
>> I think so, too. I will I mean, look,
here's the thing. I'm sure that Vladimir
Putin would
less so President Xi. I think Vladimir
Putin in his heart thinks it's an
atrocity and would like to help his
ally, but knows that it would be World
War III.
And that's the calculus for him. I I I
will say that um
I would expect the Russians and Chinese
to continue supplying the Iranians with
um air defense systems.
If But of course, they have to get them
there.
>> I mean, obviously there's going to be a
naval blockade. Yeah, definitely.
Definitely.
Um Yeah.
Another war of choice and for Israel at
that, says DH Frank. Way to go, DJT,
Donald J. Trump. Your subservience to
Israel on as that country's slim is a
disgrace.
Do you think Iran did a huge mistake at
striking other countries like Qatar, the
UAE, and others?
Prantik Amire says.
You know, it's an interesting That is a
good question, right? Cuz you can see
that you can you can argue it either
way.
>> [snorts]
>> Yeah.
I mean, I think the I think the
advantage of it I think there is some
advantage to it though. I mean,
tactically, if you take out like
airfields in those Gulf states, that's
those are facilities that are no longer
available for the US or the Israelis to
use for like refueling and resupplying
and stuff like that.
You're not losing any allies that you
had before. These are These were not
your friends to begin with. It's for
domestic consumption, too. Like, we're
not just taking it and you know, we're
we're going to we're striking back
against all the [__] I guess the
the counter
the the counter is of course you are
making new enemies
in the population that you might not
have had before. I don't know. What do
you think?
Yeah, I think that's that's right. I
want to add to Al Jazeera now is
reporting that one person was killed in
Abu Dhabi
after several missiles launched from
Iran were intercepted.
Uh
I would assume he was killed by falling
debris, which would not be unusual.
Bahrain said
a missile attack targeted the US Fifth
Fleet headquarters, which is right there
on the water in the capital city of
Manama. And Kuwait's defense minister
said that the US airbase, the Ali Al
Salem airbase, is currently under
attack. But so far all of the Iranian
missiles have been intercepted by
Kuwaiti air defenses.
Mhm.
Oh, and and the Saudi foreign ministry
is saying that
that Riyadh was targeted. I didn't
realize that the Iranians were going
that far inland. I thought they were
keeping it to the East Coast of Saudi
Arabia. So,
the capital city of Riyadh was was
targeted. Trump says it's
>> another thing we should be we should be
looking for, Ted, um
is uh is the continuing use of drones.
One thing that the Iranians are very
good at is [snorts]
they build their own suicide drones
right there in Iran using Iranian parts,
and they can build lots of them.
Remember all these drones that they sent
against against Israel back in October,
these were all homemade drones. And when
I call them suicide drones, it means
that they have explosives strapped to
them, and they are remotely flown
directly into a target where they
explode.
They're not meant to launch a missile
and then return to their base. So,
they're they they commit suicide, um so
to speak. So, Al Jazeera says that
Erbil Airport in the Kurdish region of
northern Iraq
was targeted twice overnight, and
specifically Erbil International Airport
was targeted, but air defenses
intercepted and shot down a drone there.
The reason that's important is because
the Iraqi government has said repeatedly
that it would not participate in any
American attack on Iran. Obviously, it's
close to the Iranian government.
The Kurds have autonomy in the north.
And what we could be seeing here is the
Kurds
independently supporting US action
actions against Iran and allowing the US
military, and by extent the Israeli
military, to use their base in Erbil to
attack Iran.
That's an added little twist here. I
could see that. Um Senator Mark Warner,
who's the top Democrat on the even
though they're they're a minority right
now in the Senate Intelligence
Committee,
says that the Gang of Eight, which is
sort of the traditional elite group of
senators who are briefed ahead of of
actions like this, were briefed by Marco
Rubio,
but only a few of them, and that they
weren't given any
or at least not a full accounting of the
legal justification for the attack.
John, there is no legal justification,
so I guess there's no that part.
There's no legal justification.
There's no They don't even The
administration pretended that there is a
legal justification. We're doing this
because the Israelis told us to. Yeah.
That's it.
>> I mean I mean I've always been hesitant
when people have said, "Oh, we're just
Israel's bitch." Mhm. We're Israel's
[__]
>> There it is.
Uh Chris Kahie, 1999, thanks for the
donation. Thanks for standing against
this war, John and Ted. Will Russia and
China wage a proxy war against us?
What's the likelihood of World War III?
Also, I'm dying to know what was William
F. Buckley's relationship to the CIA? A
lot of stuff there. Um will Russia and
China wage a proxy war against us?
Well, I mean we kind of are in in one in
Ukraine right now, and we could be in
one in Taiwan. I mean certainly [snorts]
one of the assessments John, you know,
we always hear this
at the agency, did you ever Did you guys
actually believe the this idea that like
when the US is tied up and in something
like this, that our adversaries think,
"Oh, this might be a good chance for me
to get away with something I might not
otherwise have been able to away with?"
Yes. That calculation is always always
in the mix.
Yes. I was never sure if that was just
you know, something they said or whether
that's something they really thought was
true.
Um
Iran can't meet the United States in
open battle, so that means irregular
warfare. John, what are the chances that
Iran will start terrorist attacks in
Israel and the West?
I think quite good.
I I the chances are high enough that we
should expect that to be
to to be the case.
>> won't be next week, you know, it could
be a year.
>> No, no, no, no, this is a long-term
thing.
It could be 5 years from now. Sure.
I mean and I and it's not necessarily
directly ordered from Tehran. It's like
this could just be self-inspired people
who are ideologically pissed off at what
we're doing and decide that, you know,
we need to be punched in the nose. Yeah.
I think that's right.
>> hey guys, glad I caught you just a
Constitution still exists seems like
it's turned into an objective object.
It's um it's you know what it's like,
John? It's sort of like how on the New
Jersey Turnpike the speed limit is 55
but no one drives under 80. It's a
suggestion but it's not really enforced.
You're not going to get a speeding
ticket unless you're going well over 90.
That's what the Constitution has become.
Yep.
Um Yep, yep.
>> have time and time
Ted Koba. You guys have time and time
again praised Trump but now you're mad?
Now that the loose cannon that everyone
has has warned you will blow up, you're
mad? I actually very appreciate that
criticism. Seriously, I'm not kidding.
Um I we have I I don't think it's fair
to say that we have been lickspittles of
the of this president. Um I think we
both First of all, I didn't vote for
him. I voted for Jill Stein to the left
of Kamala Harris. Um I but I mean we're
not Trumpies but we're also willing to
give this president his due when he does
something right. Um and I don't think
that that makes us, you know,
ass lickers of the administration. I
don't know. Others may disagree.
Yeah.
I mean the other day I said nice things
about Hillary Clinton for the way she
handled herself when she was
disrespected
by the House Intelligence by the House
Oversight Committee. I hate Hillary
Clinton. That does not make Saying that
she did something right or that she was
a victim here does not make me a Hillary
Clinton acolyte. I don't
>> Exactly. We I I'm proud to say that both
of us just call it as we see it.
I don't have any um
I don't have any uh loyalty to to
anybody on either side. I know you don't
either. Nope. And so, you know, we're
human. Sometimes we're wrong, but we we
call it as we see it. Totally. Totally.
But, I do appreciate seriously don't
hesitate if you if you think we're we're
full of [__] to tell us. We
we'll
we'll engage you.
>> Okay. Tariq master That guy. Thanks for
the dollars. The US Okay, you already
answered that. Thanks for the emergency
pod and thank you for the 999 DH
let's see. Sorry.
Uh
that's Shawn WP. Thank you. Um Is the
Strait of Hormuz closed? Roguebot wants
to know.
>> That's a great question. Let's look that
up.
>> I I don't think that it's formally
closed, but I would guess that
>> I wouldn't send my ship I wouldn't send
my ship full of explosives through
there.
>> through there, would you? No. And I'll
tell you what normally happens in a case
like this
is Lloyd's of London will make a blanket
announcement that everybody's shipping
insurance is temporarily suspended.
Right. Right. Right. Right. They're
they're the ones who who do all major
maritime shipping.
>> Yeah.
So, get ready for the whole Rudy says if
you criticize these illegal strikes
you're for Iran propaganda. Bring it.
I want I want Iran to win. Yeah.
Okay. Okay.
>> I want Iran to win. I want them to
survive. Okay. The War Powers Resolution
requires the president that the
president communicate to Congress the
committal of troops within 48 hours.
It's immoral, not illegal.
Sorry, y'all.
Um there's more to
The War Powers Act is
>> it that's not the only thing at play
here, though, right? I mean, there's no
legal justification on The United States
has treaty obligations under
international law that we're violating
here. Yes. And as a member as a UN
Charter member state, right?
The UN was our idea.
Yeah, it was our idea. That's why it's
in New York.
Uh do you think Israel will nuke Iran
and blame the Iranian nuclear program
for the blast? Charlie, God forbid. Um I
wouldn't put anything past the Israelis.
>> No, I wouldn't either. If the Israelis
really believe that they are under
threat, that their existence is under
threat, yeah, they'll do it.
And the winds don't go toward them, so
they wouldn't care.
>> That's right, they don't care.
Um you know,
at that point I would have to say, well,
I'm already at the point where I feel
like Israel has lost its right to exist,
but um
anyway,
uh
three birds, one stone. I could be
misremembering things. Thanks for the
donation, but didn't John say one time
that Iran is under Russia's nuclear
umbrella? Is Russia in that move the
Russians right now? No, what I said was
that there were there were discussions
between the Iranians and the Russians
about bringing Iran under its nuclear
umbrella. Uh Putin stepped back from
that a couple of days after the
statement was first made.
And then everybody just assumed,
including me, that what it would mean at
the end of the day was uh
was that it was the message that was
supposed to frighten the West away from
from making this attack. Which didn't
turn out to be the case. Dangerous
person 666, thanks for the five. Um I'm
disappointed and surprised that Albanese
and Wong from Australia refuse to
condemn crimes the US or the or Israel
commit. Today supporting this BS. Why
does our actual left-wing government
capitulate? We hate this.
I don't know enough about Australia. Do
you, John?
Uh I I doubt that I know any more than
you do.
Okay. Um do we think terrorists are
Christians or Jews?
>> sorry. Let me let me add one thing.
Um Albanese, for all his opposition
credentials
uh is pro-American. And the
the Australians recognize that they're
the junior partner in that relationship.
And so when push comes to shove, the
Australians are going to do what the
Americans tell them to do. No doubt. Um
potassium 3502, do you think any
terrorist sleeper cells will get
activated in the US?
This is your expertise, but I'd be No.
No. I The
When I was when I was still inside, and
granted my information's old, there
there were no sleeper cells in the US.
There are most definitely sleeper cells
in places like Pakistan, Afghanistan,
Saudi Arabia. They're out there. They're
just not here.
Um Thanks guys for doing Thanks for the
Evil Robot RB. Thanks for the 10 bucks.
Thanks for doing a Saturday night
Saturday morning broadcast. Uh what
could Trump possibly be hiding in the
from in the Epstein files that he's
pulling every distraction lever
available? Aliens, ice, Iran, etc. etc.
>> Right?
>> It looks like that.
Yeah, it does. Um
uh
I I I Who knows? I mean, I got to say, I
was You know, John, I've said it over
and over. I just didn't think it was you
know, pedophilia was Trump's bag. Uh you
know, I know he likes sex, but I just
never
And um
the the reluctance to turn over half of
the of the of of the Epstein files it
well, it's re- refusal, I should say
coupled with all this distraction
and Marjorie Taylor Greene uh being
furious about what she's not telling us
everything I'm starting to reconsider
that.
Hey, Al Jazeera's just just now in the
last minute and a half
is quoting the Iranian foreign minister
about Zarqawi
as saying, and listen to this odd quote
Ayatollah Ali Khamenei is alive as far
as I know.
What are we supposed to take from that?
As far as I know.
>> about as far as he know. That that would
tend to tell me that either
communications are down or that they've
got they're on, you know, radio silence
because they don't want their their um
That could be It could be the radio
silence. He
It's It says here he added that
two commanders were killed, but most
officials remain alive.
Most officials remain alive.
And then
oddly enough, it says he also added that
there is a possibility to reach a deal
with the Americans which can guarantee
that Iran's nuclear program is peaceful.
What?
Uh we have some we have some statements
from foreigner from uh various countries
around the world. Russia,
unsurprisingly, condemned the uh the war
against Iran as a reckless step and a
deliberate, premeditated, and unprovoked
act of armed um aggression. Zelenskyy is
all about it. He said it's important
that the US is acting decisively.
Uh this understanding must also come to
the Russians. In the end, he said the
Middle East region will become safer and
more stable. Man, you got to go back to
your comedy show, Zelenskyy, if you
think that. Um the uh president of
Finland, Alexander Stubb, said recent
events are very deeply worrying.
Ensuring nuclear safety and long-term
security is of the utmost importance. We
condemn all actions to escalate the
conflict in the region.
Ireland said he's deeply concerned and
also is concerned about escalation.
Viktor Orbán of Hungary said the strikes
on Iran have doubled the importance of
the friendship oil pipeline uh that runs
through Ukraine and supplies Russian oil
to Slovakia and Hungary. Albania uh
Prime Minister Edi Rama says he stands
firm with Israel and supports the US.
The E3, France, Germany, and the UK said
they're in close contact with their
partners
um and condemned Iran's retaliatory
attacks. Mike Johnson, the speaker of
the House of Representatives, and
without a doubt the biggest lickspittle
to Donald Trump in the world, said that
that Trump and the administration have
made every effort to pursue peaceful and
diplomatic solutions in response to the
Iranian regime's sustained nuclear
ambition, support for terrorism, and the
murder of Americans and even their own
people. [__]
Um
Dinky 33, thank you very, very much for
1,800 UAE dirhams.
Thank you for that very much. And and
Taty Marie
um please pray for the sailors in the
region. Such senseless loss of life for
a war of choice. We deserve better
leaders. Hope your Lent is going well.
Thank you for that. And and same to you,
and I couldn't agree agree more with
your statement. Ted, may I add one
thing? Please. Um this also just in from
Al Jazeera. One of the targeted is one
of the targeted sites in Tehran is
Narmak to the east, believed to be the
residence of former populist president
Mahmoud Ahmadinejad.
Now, listen.
>> He's the former president.
He's not in any position of authority.
He's retired.
He was a moderate, too.
>> Targeting him is simply an act of
murder.
>> That's it. It's gratuitous. It's
gratuitous. It would be like going to
war against Afghanistan and and killing
Hamid Karzai. Exactly. Who is still
living in Kabul. Um Yes.
Um John, how would most of the CIA be
reacting to all this? Scared, excited,
genuinely curious?
That's a great question. It was my
experience um during the Iraq war that
people put their heads down and did as
they were told. I remember my boss
telling a an assembled group, "We're not
here to take a political position one
way or another, because we all opposed
the Iraq war." He said, "We're not here
to take a political position one way or
another. We are not a policy
organization. We're a policy support
organization. And so, we are going to do
what we are told by the White House to
do."
And my guess is they've had the same
conversation today. Rudy, if this call
if this goes poorly, which there's a
chance it will, oh, higher higher better
than 50/50, I'd say, this all but
destroys J.D. Vance's 2028 presidential
hopes. You know, that's a great That's a
great point. I agree with that. Because
J.D. Vance, first of all, he's
to quote Christopher Moltisanti, he's
the heir apparent, number one. Number
two,
number two, what makes it really hard
for a vice president, the sitting vice
president, to run for president at the
end of his president's term is the very
first question from reporters is,
"When did you disagree with the
president?"
Tell us give us an example of when you
disagreed with the president. He's not
going to be able to see say he ever
disagreed with Donald Trump. That would
be political suicide. Right.
>> Well, this is a That was a Kamala Harris
question that she couldn't answer.
>> Exactly. And And it's a question that's
asked of of every of every sitting vice
president who's running for president.
And so, he's not going to be able to
answer.
If anything, this gives
this gives Marco Rubio an opening. And
Rubio said something very interesting
two days ago. He said that
um he will not run for president uh if
it looks like J.D. Vance is going to be
the nominee. Well, you don't know if
J.D. Vince Vance is going to be the
nominee until you run against him.
And so,
I think that Rubio's lying to us. I
think that he will run for president. I
think that J.D. Vance is young and
inexperienced, and I think that he will
get swallowed up in a national campaign.
I think that the the John McCain wing of
the Republican Party is ascendant again,
that MAGA was was a blip, and it was
tied more to Donald Trump's personality
than it was to any any wave of political
change.
And so, it's straight back to the not
even back. It's a continuation of the
bad old days.
If you're just joining us, we're
covering the US and Israeli
attack against Iran. By the way, a new
statement from the Iranian government.
The governor of Mindab County, where
that strike against the girl's school in
southern Iran took place, now says the
death toll has risen to at least 63
students with a further 92 injured. This
was during daylight when the school was
in session
when it was packed with students.
According to the foreign minister, Abbas
Araghchi,
posting on X. Asked about the strike,
CENTCOM did not deny it. They said that
they were aware of these reports and are
looking into them.
Um, that's horrible.
>> Looking into them.
Does that tell you that they're just
offering up lip service, or does that
tell you that it was an Israeli missile
that did it? It's an Israeli missile. I
thought so, too.
>> 100%.
>> The Israelis specifically target
civilians. Yeah, no, that's that's they
Yeah, they're into total war as they
used to call it during World War II.
DH Rank 999, president, senators, and
congressmen are
habitual short-term thinkers. I think
this has disastrous long-term
geopolitical implications. Yes, I agree
with that. Can you briefly discuss the
geopolitical implications of this war?
Well,
I mean, first of all, this is going to
put a lot of Do you tell me? I think
this is going to put a lot of Sunni
governments
kind of like on their backs on their
back heel,
where they're going to have more of a
division with their citizens
over Israel and the United States and
their relationships with them than they
did in the past, right? I mean, I think
this is going to have
>> [clears throat]
>> This is also going to
you know, attach us, like I said at the
beginning of this of this edition. It It
joins us at the hip to to Israel. I
mean, we are now, you know, we're not
like their allies supporting them in
their attack against the people next
door in Gaza and the West Bank. We're
now joining them in attacking the
biggest, most powerful country in the
Middle East.
Hey, you want to hear something crazy?
While we're talking about this, while
Israel is hunkering down and waiting for
the Iranian response,
the Israeli military is bombing Southern
Lebanon right now.
Always
the devil is always busy, as Robbie
likes to say. Uh, Phil Pentagious, thank
you very much for joining the the show.
Much appreciate your membership you
getting becoming a member. Um,
uh, we are, by the way, number six in
the nation on Rumble right now, John.
Um, I believe this operation was one in
which Russia was well aware of, and this
will grow
draw global interest to the Mideast, and
I believe Trump is on the same page as
Putin. What? Russia de- defeats UK,
>> US and Russia.
No. I totally disagree with that.
>> so.
Um, what is it that former CIA like
Sarah Adams see that John doesn't?
I think Sarah Adams is nuts, to tell you
the truth. Sarah Adams never had access
to classified information. She was She
was an open-source analyst analyzing
press, and she's made quite a handsome
living for herself by predicting
imminent disaster.
That's why people flock to her. They're
like, "Oh my god, she's from CIA, and
she's saying that the terrorist cells
are going to be destroy us."
That's how she makes a living. She never
had access to classified documents.
Um, Iran might be waiting Two Thanks
Huck's Lex for the two bucks. Iran might
be waiting for nightfall to unleash.
It's possible. I mean, yeah, it's it's
currently what? It's about a 7-hour time
difference, something like that?
>> No, it's a How How What's the time
difference with Iran?
8 hours. Okay, so it's So, that means
it's currently 6:00 in the evening
in Tehran.
Um
Yeah, I mean it night night's not going
to fall for another 2 hours.
Uh we'll see.
Um
Peachy Pie, I think you're full of [__]
half the time hahaha, but I still like
watching you guys. Okay, thanks that
you know, just keep just keep watching.
Uh super tell for 999 do we think that
the CIA is prepping the um Kurds and the
Taliban to proxy invade Iran in place of
ground troops or the US is the US
prepping Delta to perform a similar
operation in Venezuela. Certainly not
the Taliban. I'll I'll weigh in on that.
No. Alex Pierce, thank you very much for
the uh the $50. Very grateful. Thank
you.
Um Iran winning means more Americans
will die. I don't support this military
action in any form. Fuggy says, but now
that it's happened, I don't think it's
appropriate that you say you want Iran
to be victorious. You know, I don't
think it's quote-unquote appropriate,
but when your government is the
aggressor
uh in a war of choice and there's only
going to be this I kind of feel like the
people who say there's only two
political parties you have to vote for
one, but there's only two there's only
well, there's only two sides here. Yeah.
One's going to win and one's going to
lose. I don't want the aggressor who's
acting illegally to win. So, you know, I
mean I do feel
I love my country. I don't love my
government. I want my government to fail
in this endeavor. I don't want any
Americans to lose their lives in this
endeavor. I don't want any Iranians to
lose their lives in this endeavor or for
that many any Israelis to lose their
lives in this endeavor. This is all it's
just really pointless and hopeless, but
I understand what you're saying, but I'm
I just respectfully disagree.
Um Susan, I wonder if this will
ultimately drive the US economy into the
ground.
Well, you war can do that.
Yeah.
Um, can we make a distinction between
Iran and the Iranian regime? Putting
Iranians in the same box is like putting
Americans in the same box as the far
left party present here.
Yeah, well, that's it's shorthand,
right? When we say the Iranians in in
the in the context of a war, we're
talking about the government. We're not
talking about the people.
That's right. Uh, Al Jazeera is on the
side of the US and Israel against Iran,
so I wouldn't really trust them right
now, says long-time listener.
Not true.
Why would you think Al Jazeera is
reliable information? Aris wants to
know.
Because they have people on the ground.
And they've they've proven to be solid
reporters. It Al Jazeera has a very long
history. It's been around a long time,
decades. And uh
you know, three and a half decades, and
they have they have proven uh that they
have good reporters, good analysis, and
they have people on the ground in these
war zones. Cameron, it says Iran's
retaliation hit US bases across multiple
Gulf states, even striking the US fifth
fleet service center in Bahrain. What
does it tell you about Iran's escalation
ladder and its confidence?
I I do think that the Iranians uh have
the ability, at least for the time
being, to retaliate. Uh they they can't
retaliate over the long term, of course,
because their resources are finite. But,
you know, they said they would inflict
as much pain as they could in the event
that they were attacked, and that's
>> That's what we're seeing today. They
kind of have to, otherwise what's the
point of having a military?
>> That's right. Uh Tripti, thanks for the
five bucks. Um
Uh
Good morning, a non-war question for
you, John, from Sir Bikes-A-Lot. Thanks
for the donation. Can you explain the AI
that you use and why? I have a friend
who pays for ChatGPT.
Yeah, uh sure. I use Perplexity. I find
it to be far superior to ChatGPT.
ChatGPT lies about me. It just makes
stuff up. And um
Yeah, and I don't like it. And it's been
my experience that Perplexity
for whatever reason, reasons I don't
fully understand, Perplexity offers much
deeper analysis when I ask it to look at
things. Yeah, I think Perplexity is
trained on a lot of academic uh white
papers and stuff.
>> That that would make perfect sense
because that's what I've used it for.
Feral dogs, these guys love Kamala
Harris for 2028. I don't know who these
guys are, but it ain't John and I.
Not a chance, man. Um Yikur Huskav, uh
John, uh thanks for the fiver. Do you
think the Iranians can utilize maritime
drones uh to defeat defeat US ships in
the same way the US the Ukrainians
disabled the Russian fleet in the Black
Sea?
>> [snorts]
>> You know, that's a good question, and
it's a hard question to answer. If they
have enough drones, yeah, they can make
an impact. Uh you know,
ships are are notoriously um excellent
at defending themselves from incoming uh
threats. But a ship has only so many
defensive missiles on it. If if you send
a drone against a ship as the Iranians
did a week ago, we're going to shoot it
down. If you send 500 drones against a
ship, you can't shoot all of them down.
It's uh so basically these are like
yeah, these are like remote-controlled
uh well, they're torpedoes, basically.
>> Yeah, they're essentially slow-motion
torpedoes. That's right. Um
I like this question, Cameron. John, if
you still inside the the CIA, what would
be the single most alarming indicator
you'd be watching right now?
Uh the movement of ground forces.
You know, we we only have, I'm going to
say, 50,000 troops in the region. You
can't invade a country of 92 million
people with 50 with 50,000 troops. If we
started moving hundreds of thousands of
troops to bases in Saudi Arabia, Kuwait,
the United Arab Emirates, I would be
genuinely worried. And there's also talk
of of taking the the only other active
um aircraft carrier strike force battle
group that we have and moving it to the
region. That would frighten me. John,
I'm I'm I'm able to continue a little
bit if you are, but it's up to you.
Yeah, you mind I I've got to drive to
New York, but let's let's do another 10
minutes. Okay,
and thank you everyone for watching this
special edition of Deep Program with Ted
Rall and John Kiriakou for Saturday,
February 28th covering the US and
Israeli attack against Iran.
Um
so, uh I like this question a lot, Ali.
I have a more abstract question. How
much does
Israel truly gain from provoking Iran
like this? I understand the goal of a
coup and how that benefits, I mean, that
won't happen, but is that really what
this is? Full-on war?
You know, that's a great question.
The from the Israeli side,
the only thing that the Israelis could
call a victory is the complete overthrow
and removal of the Iranian government.
Anything less and the Israelis lose.
Which brings us to this comment from
Joseph. Iran needs to survive, not win.
That's right.
>> Exactly right.
That is exactly right.
>> famous conversation between Dulles and
Ho Chi Minh, right? Like, you know, you
will you will win you Americans will win
every battle and we will win the war.
Um
Um A6 killer, my brother's work at
Shannon Airport in Ireland, which is
used as a refueling base for American
troops on their way to the Middle East.
I'll ask him to keep an eye out for an
uptick. That's important and I'm I'm
glad to read that because I'm reminded
of a conversation I had yesterday with a
friend in Cyprus.
And she told me that something's going
on at the British Air Force base there,
Akrotiri.
She said they don't release any
information, of course, and the the
British, you know, have had it for 100
years. They've never They've never ceded
any control to the to the Cypriots, but
she said something's going on. I said,
"Oh, I can tell you what's going on.
We're getting ready to bomb Iran." And
there it is.
Um speaking of which,
Conspiracy Podcast says, "John, have you
watched Bustamante's last video about
calling you wrong on the timing of the
bombings? Plus, love your content."
Yeah, Bustamante's a clown.
And uh
>> [laughter]
>> All I can do is laugh and shake my head.
Bustamante, he's probably already
volunteered to go back and fight Iran.
Young Lock, thanks for the dollar.
Sending you this message from Ireland. I
hope these strikes These strikes are
wrong. Sorry, not I hope. These strikes
are wrong and wholly indefensible. I
hope the American people have the good
sense to vote against this in November
and in 2028 because this is awful. Um my
problem, John, is who would they vote
for? I mean, the Democratic Party is not
going to say anything sizable against
this. They're not against the war or
attacking Iran. They're just a They're
against the fact that they haven't been
brought into the briefings.
Yeah, that's exactly right.
That's it right there. It's just they
didn't invite us to the war party. And
and Newsom is pro-Israel and Shapiro,
not only is pro-Israel, but but served
in the Israeli military. There There's
not a single Democrat
Yeah, exactly. There's not a single
Democrat running for president
who
is not pro-Israel. And you can say
exactly the same thing about the
Republicans.
Yeah, there's there's no one to vote
for. And
it's very depressing. Not to mention, as
we've talked about it other contexts, I
mean, there is definitely an assault on
the idea of even having a midterm
election this year. And you know, as we
the Washington Post reported late late
last week, um you know, the
administration is considering
nationalizing the elections. I think as
a sort of first step to declaring a
national emergency to possibly not even
hold them at all. Um you know, uh
non-war question for you, John. I've
recently become fascinated with by
Kazakhstan. I never realized how
beautiful of a country it is. What's
your knowledge and experience like
there?
Well, Ted's actually the expert on
Kazakhstan, but
uh to tell you the truth, we're hoping
to get there this summer. We are. That's
right. Um
so uh yeah, Kazakhstan is a uh is is a
stunning country. I've been there many,
many times. Um and uh yeah, it's uh I
look forward to going back. Uh it is one
of the big secrets is that it's one of
the biggest new oil uh oil-rich
countries in the world.
Starting in 1999, um and it is a
fascinating country with a a rich
history, but uh you know, that's that's
for another topic. Hey, I want to thank
want to thank Sergeant Potato, too, for
the 80 Australian dollars. Thank you
very much. He says, "John, I'm a big
fan. Started listening to your podcast
in 2024 and your stories are incredible.
The way you tell them makes me feel like
I'm right there in the room." That's
exactly what my goal is. Wishing you all
the success. Thank you very much for
that. And um
there was something uh
John, do you have an official TikTok
account? There are quite a few people
impersonating you there. Robbie, do I
have an official TikTok account? Let me
put Robbie on. Hold on.
You do. It's going to be going live
tomorrow. So, you do have an official
TikTok account and you are all you also
have an official Rumble account. All of
your shorts are going to be blasting
across on Instagram, TikTok, and here on
Rumble, as well as YouTube. Awesome.
Thank you, Robbie.
Okay, uh some some just some updates. Um
British planes, according to US UK Prime
Minister Keir Starmer, says the British
planes are in the sky and over the
Middle East to participate in
coordinated defense efforts to protect
British interests and allies.
Um, the Senate Majority Leader Tom John
Thune praised Trump for his attack
against Iran. Um, and he said that he's
looking forward to a briefing for all of
the US senators. Um, and finally
uh, maybe not finally, but um, Iran is
believed now to have thousands of
missiles and drones uh, in its stockpile
ready to strike throughout the entire
region according according to CNN
analysis.
Yeah, this is not going to be short.
I've got breaking news coming in. It
looks like that there has there been a
drone or a missile strike in the Palma
district of Dubai. [__] Uh, it looks
like a hotel is gone.
Wow. Or at least a building next to next
to a hotel.
And [snorts] the Kuwait International
Airport is currently under attack. So,
um, Iran is definitely fighting back.
Well, I guess you have nothing to lose.
Yeah, and they're fighting
>> should um, you go um, hell is what I
would do. If you're going to kill me,
I'm going to do as much damage as I
possibly can.
Oh my god.
I'm going to I'm I'm going to
text a friend of mine in Dubai right
right now.
Oh my god.
Yeah, it looks like it's it it is
actively happening as we speak.
And you know Sorry, go ahead. Sorry, the
Telegraph, the UK paper, is reporting
that uh, missiles are being seen flying
to and fro over Dubai.
Oh my god almighty.
Let's see.
Just looking for some more stuff here.
Uh, looks like the Kuwaiti Airport was
actually hit.
I just flew in and out of Kuwait 3 weeks
ago.
Flew in and out of Dubai a week ago.
Uh launches near I'm going to butcher
this name Qom, Q O M. Qom, the holy city
of Iran. Yeah, Qom.
Uh looks like it's a it is a swarm of
ballistic missiles that uh people are
recording taking off. So, I don't know
where they're going, but they're going
somewhere. Qom is uh
is the most important city in Iran for
the study of uh of Islam and uh it it's
also something of an industrial city.
To me, there's no reason to hit a city
like Qom. There are no Iranian air force
bases there, for example.
Um unless you're trying to
destroy civilian infrastructure.
Uh oil refinery in Saudi Arabia just
went up. Oh my god, this is What are you
looking at?
Uh I am looking at Middle East Spectator
over on Telegram. And I'm also looking
at the here I will send you I will
forward this over to you right now.
And I'm also looking at some Russian
Telegram channels and they are
just uh
they're sending stuff as we speak.
>> [sighs]
>> Uh there's uh footage online right now
of people celebrating and dancing in Tel
Aviv. I bet they are.
[__] them.
That's that's that's my message to you.
If you're an Israeli, [__] you.
From America.
This is your war, not mine.
Yeah.
Yeah. Ro Khanna,
2028.
Man.
Well, it is as bad as we thought it was
going to be.
Yeah. Yeah. Well, totally. So, I guess
we're going to watch this genre you
traveling today or Yeah, I'm going to
jump in the car now. All right. So,
maybe we can do this tomorrow. We'll
see.
This is no promises. This was a
spontaneous thing. We saw what was going
on and we thought we needed to hop on.
So, thank you everyone for watching.
Best of our our thoughts and prayers as
they say to the people of Iran and
we I apologize on behalf of our country,
really. And
you know, it's going to be a rough few
days at least.
Guys, thanks so much for watching and
supporting DProgram with Ted Rall and
John Kiriakou.
We will be back as scheduled on Monday
at 9:00 a.m. Eastern time. That's when
we air Monday through Friday 9:00
o'clock Eastern time. John, safe
travels. Robbie, talk to you later and
we'll if there's more to bring you and
we're able to do it, we will pipe in
like we did just now and otherwise have
a great weekend.
Bye. Bye, everybody.
>> [music]
[music]